<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="sys_metadata_link">
    <sys_metadata_link action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <directory>update</directory>
        <documentkey>18bddf2edb6ca158b1227ea5f396196d</documentkey>
        <payload><![CDATA[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><record_update table="x_g_dis_atat_dapps_dummy_data">
    <x_g_dis_atat_dapps_dummy_data action="INSERT_OR_UPDATE">
        <content>&lt;?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?&gt;&#13;
&lt;ProcurementDocument&gt;&#13;
    &lt;SchemaVersionUsed&gt;2.5.1&lt;/SchemaVersionUsed&gt;&#13;
    &lt;ProcurementInstrumentForm&gt;DD 1155&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentForm&gt;&#13;
    &lt;OriginatorDetails&gt;&#13;
        &lt;InternalDocumentNumber&gt;878317&lt;/InternalDocumentNumber&gt;&#13;
        &lt;DoDSystem&gt;&#13;
            &lt;DITPRNumber&gt;00000431&lt;/DITPRNumber&gt;&#13;
            &lt;SystemAdministratorDoDAAC&gt;HQ0034&lt;/SystemAdministratorDoDAAC&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/DoDSystem&gt;&#13;
    &lt;/OriginatorDetails&gt;&#13;
    &lt;AwardInstrument&gt;&#13;
        &lt;ProcurementInstrumentHeader&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentOrigin&gt;Department of Defense&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentOrigin&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentVehicle&gt;Delivery Order&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentVehicle&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;EnterpriseIdentifier&gt;HQ0034&lt;/EnterpriseIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Year&gt;21&lt;/Year&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProcurementInstrumentTypeCode&gt;F&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentTypeCode&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;SerializedIdentifier&gt;0024&lt;/SerializedIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentDescription&gt;Represented Contract&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentDescription&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentIdentifier&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentOrigin&gt;Department of Defense&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentOrigin&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentVehicle&gt;Indefinite Delivery Indefinite Quantity&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentVehicle&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;EnterpriseIdentifier&gt;HQ0034&lt;/EnterpriseIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Year&gt;21&lt;/Year&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProcurementInstrumentTypeCode&gt;D&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentTypeCode&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;SerializedIdentifier&gt;0002&lt;/SerializedIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentDescription&gt;Ordering Instrument&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentDescription&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentIdentifier&gt;&#13;
            &lt;BasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;TransmissionAcknowledgement&gt;Acknowledge Receipt With No Detail and Change&lt;/TransmissionAcknowledgement&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentName&gt;Delivery Order (DD 1155)&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentName&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ContingencyContract&gt;false&lt;/ContingencyContract&gt;&#13;
                &lt;DocumentPurpose&gt;Original&lt;/DocumentPurpose&gt;&#13;
                &lt;EmergencyRequestContract&gt;false&lt;/EmergencyRequestContract&gt;&#13;
                &lt;MiscellaneousTextDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;MiscellaneousText&gt;Descriptions and Specifications&#13;
TO PERFORMANCE WORK STATEMENT&#13;
TASK ORDER 0001 PERFORMANCE WORK STATEMENT&#13;
&#13;
OFFICE OF THE UNDERSECRETARY OF DEFENSE FOR RESEARCH AND ENGINEERING (OUSD(R&amp;amp;E))&#13;
RDT&amp;amp;E ENGINEERING AND TECHNICAL SUPPORT (RETS)&#13;
DIRECTORATE OF DEFENSE RESEARCH AND ENGINEERING FOR ADVANCED CAPABILITIES (DDR&amp;amp;E(AC))&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 1: DESCRIPTION OF SERVICES/GENERAL INFORMATION&#13;
&#13;
1.1&amp;#9;Mission and Background&#13;
The Directorate of Defense Research and Engineering for Advanced Capabilities (DDR&amp;amp;E (AC)) recognizes, identifies, explores, and ensures the development, integration, and funding of new technology and capabilities to maintain U.S. technological superiority. It takes a unified, missions-level view across the entire DoD enterprise to analyze joint missions and identify cross-cutting technology gaps critical to military readiness. It maintains a focus on the innovative application of technology and works with a robust network of transition partners within and external to the DoD to mitigate gaps through accelerated prototyping, demonstration, and fielding, with the ultimate goal of operational sustainment.&#13;
&#13;
OUSD(R&amp;amp;E) requires mission engineering, analysis, and integration expertise to produce objective insights and analytic justification to inform future technology and capability investment decisions within the Planning, Programming, and Budgeting Execution (PPBE) process and aid in the prioritization, alignment and validation of requirements within Joint Capabilities Integration and Development System (JCIDS) to deliver modernized capabilities that enable an all domain joint force aligned with future Joint Warfighting Concepts.  &#13;
&#13;
1.2&amp;#9;Scope&#13;
The scope of this task is to provide the range of RDT&amp;amp;E technical and engineering services required to assist DDR&amp;amp;E (AC) in accomplishing its mission. This Task Order (TO) Performance Work Statement (PWS) outlines requirements to complement and support OUSD (R&amp;amp;E)&amp;#8217;s mission. To meet these requirements, the Contractor shall provide the specialized knowledge and skill sets articulated in this TO PWS.  Additional tasks not explicitly described in this TO PWS, may be ordered under the RETS IDIQ, if necessary.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 2: DEFINITIONS&#13;
&#13;
CAC: &amp;#9;Common Access Card &#13;
CO: &amp;#9;Contracting Officer&#13;
CONUS:&amp;#9;Continental United States&#13;
COR:&amp;#9;Contracting Officer Representative &#13;
CPAF:&amp;#9;Cost Plus Award Fee&#13;
FFP:&amp;#9;Firm Fixed Price&#13;
FPAF:&amp;#9;Fixed Price Award Fee&#13;
IDIQ:&amp;#9;Indefinite Delivery / Indefinite Quantity &#13;
NCR:&amp;#9;National Capital Region&#13;
NDS:&amp;#9;National Defense Strategy&#13;
OCI:&amp;#9;Organizational Conflict of Interest &#13;
OCONUS: &amp;#9;Outside the Contiguous United States &#13;
PWS:&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Performance Work Statement &#13;
QASP:&amp;#9;Quality Assurance Surveillance Plan &#13;
QC:&amp;#9;Quality Control&#13;
RETS:&amp;#9;RDT&amp;amp;E Engineering and Technical Services &#13;
S&amp;amp;T:&amp;#9;Science and Technology&#13;
TO:&amp;#9;Task Order&#13;
&#13;
Unless otherwise defined within this PWS, &amp;#8220;days&amp;#8221; shall mean business days.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 3: GOVERNMENT FURNISHED&#13;
&#13;
The Government shall provide facilities, equipment, materials, and/or services, as required to complete tasking. At the request of the Government, or on completion of the TO under which the Government furnished equipment or information, the Contractor will immediately return any property provided by the Government used to complete the tasking. Performance on the TO may also require the Contractor to access and use material and information such as studies, reports, and key data considered proprietary to a Government agency or Contractor, which is of such a nature that its dissemination or use, other than in performance of this effort, would be adverse to the interests of the Government and/or others. If this is determined to be necessary, the contractor will be required to sign a non-disclosure agreement prior to commencement of the work.&#13;
&#13;
3.1 Services/Equipment: The Government will provide IT support to maintain government furnished IT equipment that may include laptops and smart phones.  Government furnished equipment provided in support of this TO that will be removed from the government facilities is considered property (GFP).  GFP will be processed by and maintained by the COR in accordance with the GFP procedures. See IDIQ contract Government Property clauses.  &#13;
&#13;
3.2 Utilities:  The Government will provide all utilities in the government facility to be available for the contractor&amp;#8217;s use in performance of tasks outlined in this PWS.  The contractor shall instruct employees in utilities conservation practices.&#13;
&#13;
3.3 Facilities: The Government will furnish necessary workspace for the mission engineering war room in the Mark Center that will include up to five hot desks, and limited hot desk access in the Pentagon for use by the contractor.  All Common Access Cards (CACs) will be issued on an as needed basis, and are considered Government property that must be returned immediately upon expiration of the order.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 4: CONTRACTOR FURNISHED&#13;
&#13;
The contractor shall provide all equipment, supplies, facilities, transportation, tools, materials, and other items and non-personal services necessary to perform technical, analytical, financial, administrative, and specialized support as defined in this TO PWS except for those items specified in Part 3 of this PWS.  The contractor shall perform to the standards in this contract.&#13;
&#13;
Specifically, the contractor shall supply all workspace, and computing resources up to TS/TK/SCI needed to accomplish the task independent of government facilities.  The contractor will maintain a dedicated video teleconference capability up to Secret level across all workspaces under this contract.  &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 5: REQUIREMENTS&#13;
&#13;
5.1&amp;#9;Period of Performance&#13;
This TO will be twelve (12) months in length (1 Base Year) and may extend up to six (6) months past the ordering period (ceiling considerations notwithstanding).&#13;
&#13;
5.2&amp;#9;Place(s) of Performance&#13;
The Contractor shall supply the contractor facility up to TS/TK/SCI needed to accomplish the task independent of government facilities.  Support may include other Continental United States (CONUS) and Outside the CONUS (OCONUS) locations as required by specific technical requirements. Contractor shall maintain a facility located in the proximity of the Pentagon/Mark Center with walking access to public transportation that allows transport between facilities nominally within 30 minutes.  The Government may require daily or persistent presence of key personnel within the Suffolk Building, Mark Center or Pentagon spaces to facilitate interaction with government customers and stakeholders.  The government will furnish facilities for the mission engineering war room in the Mark Center, and limited access in the Pentagon for use by the Contractor.  See Part 3 and 4 for details.  &#13;
&#13;
5.3 Hours of Operation  &#13;
The contractor is responsible for conducting business during regular Government core hours Monday thru Friday except Federal holidays or when the Government facility is closed due to local or national emergencies, administrative closings, or similar Government directed facility closings.  The contractor must at all times maintain an adequate workforce for the uninterrupted performance of all tasks defined within this PWS when the Government facility is not closed for the above reasons.  When hiring personnel, the contractor shall consider its impact to the stability and continuity of the workforce.&#13;
&#13;
5.4 Observance of Legal Holidays and Facility Closures &#13;
The contractor may be required or authorized to work when their assigned facility is on holiday or closed. The following is a list of U.S. Federal holidays and reasons for facility closures:&#13;
&#13;
New Year&amp;#8217;s Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;January 1&#13;
Martin Luther King&amp;#8217;s Birthday&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Third Monday in January&#13;
Inauguration Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;January 20, 2021 (*Only in Washington, DC)&#13;
President&amp;#8217;s Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Final Monday in February&#13;
Memorial Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Final Monday in May&#13;
Independence Day&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;July 4&#13;
Labor Day&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;First Monday in September&#13;
Columbus Day&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Second Monday in October&#13;
Veteran&amp;#8217;s Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;November 11&#13;
Thanksgiving Day &amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Fourth Thursday in November&#13;
Christmas Day&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;December 25&#13;
&#13;
Any other day/time designated by Federal statute, Executive Order, or Presidential Proclamation. Adverse weather conditions or national emergencies may require Government facilities to close. During periods of inclement weather, the contractor will be provided the DoD policy.  &#13;
&#13;
5.5 Specific Task Areas&#13;
The contractor shall provide Professional Technical and Engineering Services in the areas of Mission Integration Management and Mission Engineering.  The contractor shall be directly responsible for ensuring the accuracy, timeliness, and completion of all requirements under this PWS.  The number, type, and essential skills for contractor personnel shall be dictated by the tasks described below.  Contractor personnel will be required to interact with personnel and senior leadership from OSD, Joint Staff, FFRDC/UARCs and Industry.  The contractor will provide an overall team lead and subject matter experts with recent and relevant experience to support the OUSD(R&amp;amp;E)/DDR&amp;amp;E(AC) organization. &#13;
&#13;
The Contractor will provide support for the overall management, development, and maintenance of the mission engineering, analysis, and integration to deliver modernized capabilities that enable an all domain joint force aligned with future Joint Warfighting Concepts.&#13;
&#13;
5.5.1 Task 1:  Mission Integration Management:  The contractor shall develop, manage, and maintain mission engineering capabilities.  This effort includes:&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.1 Mission Engineering Activity Coordination &amp;amp; Planning.  The contractor shall develop and maintain a network of mission engineering points of contact within the Department to facilitate communication and integration of mission engineering activities.  The contractor shall canvass the community to establish and maintain a list, schedule, and USD(R&amp;amp;E) engagement strategy for ongoing and future mission engineering studies and activities across the Department.    &#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.2 Stakeholder Integration. The contractor shall support engagement and integration of mission engineering activities across a range of stakeholders and customers.  Integration activities involve: reviewing stakeholder artifacts and staff packages, meeting preparation for government officials, participating and representing USD(R&amp;amp;E) interests in meetings, monitoring and reporting on external activities, sharing USD(R&amp;amp;E) mission engineering products, integrating plans, and soliciting input for USD(R&amp;amp;E) mission engineering activities.  Integration venues and anticipated workload include:&#13;
&#13;
1.2.1 Joint Capabilities Integration and Development System (JCIDS) &amp;#8211; Participate in up to four working level meetings per week, prepare government officials for one to two meetings per week, review and prepare recommendations for up to four JCIDS documents per month, and provide input and review of CBAs.  &#13;
&#13;
1.2.2 Joint Force Integration Cell (JFIC) - Participate in three to four working level meetings per week, prepare government officials for one to two meetings per week, track four supporting concepts groups, review and prepare recommendations for up to two associated Joint Warfighting Concepts documents per month.   &#13;
&#13;
1.2.3 Joint All-Domain Command and Control (JADC2) &amp;#8211; Participate in three to four JADC2 working meetings per week, provide weekly highlights to government officials, assist with development of talking points / info papers to senior R&amp;amp;E leadership.&#13;
&#13;
1.2.4 Wargaming / Table Top Exercises (TTX) &amp;#8211; Support the development of joint CONOPs / CONEMPS to include participating in one workshop event per month; assist with scenario development and technology/capability content; attend exercises and help develop AARs / POAMs to address findings/results &amp;#8211; assess impact to plans, policies, strategy, procedures and incorporate outcomes into mission engineering analysis.&#13;
&#13;
1.2.5 Service / COCOM Engagement &amp;#8211; Participate in two meetings per month to understand/coordinate Services and COCOMs mission engineering requirements; work with COCOMs to understand and discuss submitted integrated priority lists.&#13;
&#13;
1.2.6 Industry Engagement &amp;#8211; Support the government officials with one or two industry engagements per month to discuss mission engineering; help prepare government officials for six conferences / symposium and/or division meetings per year hosted by military/industrial associations.&#13;
&#13;
1.2.7 OUSD(R&amp;amp;E) Modernization Principal Directors (PD) &amp;#8211; Engage with PDs on a periodic basis to understand and help develop their technology roadmaps; determine ways how mission engineering can support PDs with future gap/tradeoff analysis and studies and align mission analysis plans.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.3 Government Reference Architecture (GRA).  The contactor shall develop, maintain, and curate GRAs used to communicate and guide analysis efforts, document and communicate results, and set the basis for subsequent engineering and prototyping activities. The contractor shall support Red Team activities used to validate each GRA.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.4 Knowledge Management Database. The contractor shall develop, maintain, curate, and administer access for the content of a cloud-based knowledge management system.  Content includes models, architectures, and other mission engineering artifacts.   &#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.5 Graphics/Presentation and Visualization products.  The contractor shall produce presentation material on mission engineering artifacts as required and develop and maintain a visualization capability to communicate mission engineering products.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.6 Mission Engineering War Room.  The contractor shall populate and maintain a mission engineering workspace in the Mark Center for the purposes of interfacing and communicating with the government customer and stakeholders on planning activities, mission design, and mission engineering products.  The contractor shall ensure the war room has access all products created or maintained under this task.  &#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.7 Mission Engineering Guide.  The contractor shall develop and refine the content/material used to explain the &amp;#8220;Mission Engineering&amp;#8221; concept, and how it can be used to support the requirements of the services.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.8 Digital Engineering.  The contractor shall understand the fundamental enablers that digital engineering can provide to support Mission Engineering activities. The contract will ensure that digital engineering/modeling and simulations tools are available and used when required during mission analyses to synchronize and validate impacts of system changes on the mission.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 1.9 Chief Engineer Support.  The contractor shall coordinate and support a weekly Mission Engineering team meeting &amp;#8211; collect input from team members to track action items and status of projects. The contractor shall assist government lead with Weekly Activity Report (WAR) feedback, and responses to USD (R&amp;amp;E) front office and congressional tasks.&#13;
&#13;
5.5.2 Task 2:  Mission Engineering and Analysis:  The contractor shall construct, manage, and conduct discrete mission engineering and analysis study tasks to evaluate the efficacy of legacy architectures and new technologies and capabilities applied in new mission concepts of employment to meet evolving joint mission objectives.  The contactor shall produce a comprehensive mission blueprint that documents and communicates the ways and means to achieve the recommended joint mission solution and the analytic justification for the value it provides.  The contractor shall conduct three mission engineering and analysis study tasks.  Each study effort includes: &#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.1 Study Planning.  The contractor shall develop a study plan for government approval that establishes:&#13;
&#13;
2.1.1 Mission context, mission objectives, and system boundaries and constraints&#13;
&#13;
2.1.2 Mission level MOEs, MOPs, and TPMs as mission success criteria&#13;
&#13;
2.1.3 Study approach and schedule&#13;
&#13;
2.1.4 Stakeholders, teaming approach, and external data, previous analysis results, model, and simulation needs&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.2 Concept Exploration and Alternative Solution Development.  The contractor shall work with the Joint Staff, to explore new concepts of employment, and research labs and the modernization communities and use critical thinking to explore and develop alternative and innovative solutions for study.  &#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.3 Mission and Scenario Characterization.  The contractor shall develop and coordinate a study framework for stakeholder coordination and government approval that guides the study and establishes: &#13;
&#13;
2.3.1 Mission scenarios / vignettes&#13;
&#13;
2.3.2 Red force definitions, and environments &#13;
&#13;
2.3.3 Blue force alternatives under study&#13;
&#13;
2.3.4 Assumptions and constraints on mission, blue force and red force employments&#13;
&#13;
2.3.5 Analytic methods, and necessary virtual elements to establish the analytic baseline&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.4 Analysis and Synthesis.  The contractor shall develop/acquire models and data, and use simulations to analyze the performance of legacy and alternative solutions against mission success criteria.  Outputs will show the value and efficacy of alternative and preferred solutions in terms of measures of mission effectiveness, return on investment in terms of cost, schedule and performance, and identify key findings, sensitivities, and areas of future study.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.5 Mission Blueprint.  The contractor shall develop a mission blueprint that documents the recommended approach to accomplish joint warfighter mission objectives consisting of:&#13;
&#13;
2.5.1 Mission, concept of employment, and description of the complete to-be architecture&#13;
&#13;
2.5.2 Analytic results that demonstrate the performance of the complete architecture in meeting mission objectives and return on investment beyond competing alternatives&#13;
&#13;
2.5.3 The programmatic plans for the architectural elements which include an integrated schedule and investments adjustments needed to achieve the architecture for all involved systems&#13;
&#13;
2.5.4 Engineering-level architecture products that include digital models and data to enable the necessary changes in the capability and affected systems, identify system interfaces and requirements to inform a more integrated joint requirements process, and support the development of architecture standards needed to achieve the architecture&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.6 Communicating Results.  The contractor shall prepare executive summaries and briefings of the study outcomes and present results to stakeholder.  The contractor shall also present the findings in a computational tool of choice that shows the salient features of the results.&#13;
&#13;
Subtask 2.7 Archiving Results.  The contractor shall document and deliver all study results in a government-defined format on a cloud-based knowledge management database.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 6: ADMINISTRATIVE REQUIREMENTS&#13;
&#13;
6.1&amp;#9;Travel, Costs, and Other Direct Costs &#13;
Contractor travel is required to perform the tasking of the PWS.  Work will be performed in Contractor and Government facilities located in or around the National Capital Region (NCR).  The term &amp;quot;National Capital Region&amp;quot; means cities and other units of government within the boundaries of the District of Columbia; Montgomery and Prince George&amp;#8217;s Counties in the State of Maryland; and Arlington, Fairfax, Loudoun, and Prince William Counties and the City of Alexandria in the Commonwealth of Virginia.  Travel requirements include travel to and from the Pentagon and other Government facilities within the Washington DC area; however, local TDY and daily commuting will not be reimbursed.  All travel outside the NCR requires prior COR approval/authorization and notification to the COR.  The contractor shall be reimbursed for travel to provide support outside the NCR as approved by the COR.  The contractor shall provide a written request (via e-mail) for travel to the COR prior to finalizing any travel arrangements.  All travel must be approved by the COR prior to purchase of tickets and commencement of travel.  The contractor shall be reimbursed for actual allowable, allocable, and reasonable travel costs incurred during performance of this effort in accordance with FAR 31.205-46, &amp;#8220;Travel Costs&amp;#8221;.  Requests for approval of costs in excess of maximum per diem rates in accordance with the procedures contained in FAR 31.205-46(a)(3) must be submitted to the Contracting Officer for final approval prior to commencement of travel.  The expense of travel within NCR will not be reimbursed as a part of the Travel CLINs.  Contractor will be authorized travel expenses consistent with the substantive provisions of the Joint Travel Regulation (JTR) and the limitation of funds specified in this TO.&#13;
&#13;
All ODCs associated with this TO shall be approved in writing by the COR prior to incurring costs.  The contractor may be required to procure software licenses to perform the tasking of the PWS. The contractor may be required to incur the cost of incidental items, including but not limited to the following: meeting and training supplies, CDs and books, copying and mailing.  &#13;
&#13;
The contractor shall invoice MONTHLY against each separate order.   Other ODC items, such as software or licenses, should be itemized to include Title, whether it&amp;#8217;s a License, Duration/Frequency of the item (yearly, monthly, one-time cost, etc.), Maintenance, Quantity, and any other pertinent information to include identifying the task the ODC supports.  Travel charges must be shown per person, contain location and dates, and items must be identified by subject (i.e. meals, rental car, and airfare requirements.)  Receipts for all single travel expenses of $75 or more shall accompany the invoice.  All travel expenses for this contract must comply with FAR 31.205-46 &amp;#8220;Travel costs&amp;#8221;, Federal Acquisition Regulation (FAR) 52.232-25, the JTR, and the PWS.&#13;
&#13;
6.2 Facility Clearance.&#13;
The contractor shall possess and maintain a TOP SECRET/TALENT KEYHOLE/SENSITIVE COMPARTMENTED INFORMATION (TS/TK/SCI) facility clearance from the Defense Security Service at all times during the performance of the task order.  The DD254 is provided as Attachment 3.&#13;
&#13;
6.3 Security Clearances.  &#13;
All contractor personnel, to include part-time personnel, subcontractors and independent consultants, shall possess at a minimum a DoD Final TS/SCI clearance prior to commencing work on-site and Special Access Program (SAP) clearances at the time of order award. The Task Order PM shall possess a Final TS clearance and shall be able to obtain and maintain SCI and SAP clearance eligibility.&#13;
&#13;
The contractor shall comply with all security requirements contained in the DD Form 254 (Attachment 3), &amp;#8220;Department of Defense Contract Security Classification Specification&amp;#8221;, of this contract and the terms and conditions set forth in FAR clause 52.204-2, &amp;#8220;Security Requirements&amp;#8221;, incorporated by reference. Individual task orders may specify that a comprehensive security plan is required. In addition, the contractor may be required to assist with the assessment, and/or acquisition, of facility clearances granted by DoD. The contractor should have the capability to transport classified information to and from their corporate offices and store classified materials up to &amp;#8220;SECRET&amp;#8221; level at their off-site office spaces. Security procedures will be in accordance with DoD policies.  &#13;
&#13;
The contractor will maintain a dedicated video teleconference capability up to Secret level across all workspaces under this TO. The contractor shall be capable of hosting conferences to support at minimum 20 personnel to include breakout rooms to support pertinent working groups.&#13;
&#13;
6.4 Security Requirements.  &#13;
All contractor personnel attending meetings, answering Government telephones, and working in other situations where their contractor status is not obvious to third parties are required to identify themselves as such to avoid creating an impression in the minds of members of the public that they are Government officials.  They must also ensure that all documents or reports produced by contractors are suitably marked as contractor products or that contractor participation is appropriately disclosed.  Contractor personnel will be required to obtain and wear badges in the performance of this service.  Contract personnel that need access to government systems and work locations will be issued Common Access Cards (CAC) as required.  &#13;
&#13;
Contractors are required to report to the Pentagon Force Protection Agency (PFPA) any derogatory information that may justify an unfavorable administrative action in a personnel security or building access determination.  Derogatory information includes, but is not limited to, criminal conduct, illegal drug involvement, or psychological conditions that impair judgment, reliability or trustworthiness.  Derogatory information must be provided to the Contracting Officer&amp;#8217;s Representative (COR) and Contracting Officer as promptly as possible, but in no event later than three (3) business days after the contractor becomes aware of the information.&#13;
&#13;
PFPA reserves the right and prerogative to deny and/or restrict facility and information access of any Contractor employee determined by PFPA at any time during performance to be unsuitable for access and/or present a risk of compromising sensitive Government information to which they would have access under this contract.&#13;
&#13;
A determination by PFPA that a person is not suitable to perform work under this contract is not a denial, suspension or revocation of a previously granted security clearance by another agency, nor shall it be interpreted as a direction or recommendation to the Contractor regarding the suitability of an affected individual for employment outside the scope of PFPA.&#13;
&#13;
6.4.1 Physical Security. &#13;
The contractor shall be responsible for safeguarding all government equipment, information and property provided for contractor use.  At the close of each work period, government facilities, equipment, and materials shall be secured.&#13;
&#13;
Physical access to federally controlled facilities will be required and identity verification will be in compliance with FAR 52.204-9 &amp;#8220;Personal Identity Verification of contractor Personnel&amp;#8221;.  The Government will provide facility access, required building identification, and required systems access in order for personnel to perform their duties, which is in accordance with existing Office of the Secretary of Defense (OSD) facility access security procedures.  The contractor shall complete OSD mandatory Information Assurance and Security training and comply with all Washington Headquarters Services (WHS) and OSD Operational Security guidelines and directives.&#13;
&#13;
6.4.2 Keys, Badge and Common Access Card (CACs) Control.  &#13;
The Contractor shall establish and implement methods of making sure all keys, badges and CACs issued to the Contractor by the Government are not lost or misplaced and are not used by unauthorized persons.   The Contractor shall prohibit the use of Government issued keys/key cards by any persons other than the authorized Contractor&amp;#8217;s employees.  The contractor shall prohibit the opening of locked areas by Contractor employees to permit entrance of persons other than authorized Contractor employees engaged in the performance of assigned work in those areas, or personnel authorized entrance by the Contracting Officer.&#13;
&#13;
NOTE: No keys issued to the Contractor by the Government shall be duplicated. The Contractor shall develop procedures covering key, badge and CAC control that shall be included in the Quality Control Plan. Such procedures shall include turn-in of any issued keys, badges, and CACs by personnel who no longer require access. The Contractor shall immediately report any occurrences of loss or other issues to the Contracting Officer.&#13;
&#13;
6.4.3 Lock Combinations. &#13;
The Contractor shall establish and implement methods of ensuring that all lock combinations are not revealed to unauthorized persons.  The Contractor shall ensure that lock combinations are changed when personnel having access to the combinations no longer have a need to know such combinations. &#13;
&#13;
6.4.4 Disclosure of Information. &#13;
Information made available to the Contractor by the Government for the performance or administration of this effort shall be used only for those purposes and shall not be used in any other way without the written consent of the Contracting Officer. Contractor and/or contractor personnel shall not divulge or release data or information developed or obtained in performance of this effort, until made public by the Government, except to authorized Government personnel or upon written approval of the Contracting Officer. The contractor will not use, disclose, or reproduce proprietary data that bears a restrictive legend, other than as required in the performance of efforts within this IDIQ. Nothing herein will preclude the use of any data independently acquired by the contractor without such limitations or prohibit an agreement at no cost to the Government between the contractor and the data owner which provides for greater rights to the contractor.&#13;
&#13;
The Contractor agrees to assume responsibility for protecting the confidentiality of Government records, which are not considered public information. Each Contractor or employee of the Contractor to whom information may be made available or disclosed, shall be notified in writing by the Contractor that such information may be disclosed only for purposes and to the extent authorized within the individual task order. The Contractor shall not release any information received through any task order on the IDIQ to the public, media or other unauthorized persons or organizations unless the Government has conducted the appropriate security review and granted written approval (e.g. posting information to a public website). Performance of this effort may require the contractor to access and use data and information proprietary to a Government agency or Government contractor, which is of such a nature that its dissemination or use, other than in performance of this effort, would be adverse to the interests of the Government and/or others. The contractor will sign non-disclosure agreements at the beginning of each task order certifying that none of the information received through their work on a task order many be disseminated in any manner other than as allowed in the order.&#13;
&#13;
6.5 Non-Personal Service Statement. &#13;
Contractor employees performing on task orders under this PWS will be controlled, directed, and supervised at all times by management personnel of the contractor. Contractor management will ensure that employees properly comply with the performance work standards outlined in this PWS, and within the individual task orders. Contractor employees will perform their duties independent of, and without the supervision of, any Government official. The tasks, duties, and responsibilities set forth in specific task orders may not be interpreted or implemented in any manner that results in any contractor employee creating or modifying Federal policy, obligating the appropriated funds of the U.S. Government, overseeing work of Federal employees, providing direct personal services to any Federal employee, or otherwise violating the prohibitions set forth in Part 7.5 and 37.1 of the FAR. The Government will perform the inspection and acceptance of the deliverables provided. &#13;
&#13;
6.6 Subcontracting&#13;
The contractor is encouraged to subcontract with other contractors, or subject matter experts, or otherwise obtain consultant services for the efforts defined within the PWS or to provide the expert talent needed to perform identified requirements within the task orders. As this TO is a fully set-aside for small businesses, it is the responsibility of the prime vendors to perform at least 50% of the work in terms of awarded dollar value, unless subcontracting to similarly situated small business concerns. When providing subcontractors and/or consultants, the contractor is fully responsible for their performance and cost reporting. The contractor shall provide the manpower required to manage all subcontracts and consultant efforts and to monitor subcontractor activities to the appropriate level of detail required to assure timely deliverables. A report on the performance of subcontractors shall be included as part of the required Monthly Progress Report deliverable.&#13;
&#13;
6.7 Personnel&#13;
6.7.1 Performance. &#13;
The contractor shall provide highly qualified, team oriented, cost conscious, innovative professionals dedicated to support the development, implementation, and execution of OUSD (R&amp;amp;E) projects and activities set forth in the task order. The contractor shall function as a coordinated support team in grasping complex concepts and technologies, applying critical and innovative thinking, communicating effectively, and working seamlessly across the breath of functional areas. All contractor personnel proposed shall meet the qualifications set forth as identified within the request for proposal for this task order. The task order will dictate the number, type, and essential skills for contractor personnel. The contractor shall provide personnel for both on-site support and off-site support, as needed, during normal operations and during surges, special situations, and unforeseen events and requirements. The contractor shall be able to provide the entire PWS portfolio of services across the task order. The contractor shall have the capability and resources to provide for rapid ad-hoc surge support as required by this PWS and subsequent task orders, as defined by the schedule in the task order. &#13;
&#13;
6.7.2 Training.  &#13;
The contractor shall participate in organizational training as required.  The contractor shall also complete OSD mandatory training to include but not limited to Information Assurance and Security training, Privacy Act training, and Combating Trafficking in Persons training.&#13;
&#13;
6.7.3 Positions. &#13;
The contractor is expected to attract, hire and retains a quality work force, with minimal turnover in contractor personnel. The contractor shall appoint a Task Order Program Manager (TO PM) with overall responsibility for the task order. The PM shall possess a Final TOP SECRET/SCI clearance. The PM shall be the single point of interface with the Contracting Officer Representative and any other Government officials for all matters concerning the task order including, but not limited to, technical progress, problems, program performance, schedule, cost, resources, and other program-related matters. &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4 Technical Workforce Categories.&#13;
The contractor shall provide qualified personnel for the positions under this task order.&#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.1 Task Order Project Manager (TO PM) &#13;
Task Order Project Manager shall serve as functional and technical expert as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Supports the Program Manager and is the single point of contact to manage all programmatic matters of tasker order 0001 and is responsible for managing the day-to-day operation of the task order. Experience in a supervisory capacity in planning, developing, and executing major research, engineering, and development efforts for defense organizations.  Experience in establishing strong working relationships with R&amp;amp;D program managers as well as organization leadership; tracking task order efforts to rapidly identify and resolve potential and new problems; and identifying and resolving administrative and contractual issues related to a support services contract is required. Demonstrated creativity, foresight, initiative, and mature judgment in anticipating and solving unprecedented problems.  Experience interfacing with Joint Staff, Services, and warfighters to coordinate engineering and analysis needs and analytic results is highly desired.                   &#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 10 years. &#13;
Desired: None.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI &#13;
Personnel Type: Key&#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.2 Senior Engineer&#13;
Senior Engineers shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Expert in developing system solutions to complex and challenging DoD problems.   Experience leading the planning and execution of complex mission and systems analysis efforts.  Experience leading Systems Engineering (SE) tasks including Technology Analysis and Assessment, System Definition, Systems Analysis, Systems Architecture development and architecture products for Systems of Systems (SoS), kill chain analysis, SE tradespace and analysis to define capability gaps, Modeling and Simulation activities for mission improvement, and Logistics support of Department of Defense (DoD) systems.  Experience in supporting technical, managerial or operational fields and have expert credentials or be recognized as an authority and have the mature judgement required to advise senior government personnel. Strong oral and written communication skills are required. &#13;
&#13;
Positions: Mission Analysis Lead, Mission Architect, Stakeholder Integrator&#13;
Required: Masters in a recognized engineering discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 20 years.&#13;
Desired: PhD, experience interfacing with Joint Staff, Services, and warfighters to coordinate engineering and analysis needs and analytic results, and experience as chief engineer or lead systems engineer for a major defense acquisition program development effort.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.3 Subject Matter Expert III Technology and Capabilities (TC)&#13;
Subject Matter Expert III Technology and Capabilities (TC) shall serve as functional and technical expert as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Experience and expertise in cutting edge technologies and application of technologies into new and innovative warfighting capabilities.  In-depth technical knowledge and experience with existing and future advanced DoD weapon systems and their capabilities, concept of operations, limitations, and upgrade capacities.  Areas of expertise in system capabilities, performance, and operations include: Land, sea, air, and space platforms; offensive, defensive, kinetic and directed energy weapons; sensors for ISR and fire control; cyberwarfare; communication networks; electromagnetic spectrum management to include EW and 5G; application of automation; command, control, and battle management; fires close air support, long range fires, targeting, air and missile defense.&#13;
&#13;
Required: Masters in a recognized engineering or physics discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 20.&#13;
Desired: PhD&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.4 Subject Matter Expert I Technology and Capabilities (TC)&#13;
Subject Matter Expert III Technology and Capabilities (TC) shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Experience and expertise in Joint Force design, development and application, operational constraints, concepts of operation, concepts of employment, development and execution of COCOM operational plans, threat tactics and responses, logistics approaches. &#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors from War College or equivalent, in a recognized discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 15 years of Operations experience. &#13;
Desired: Experience working in Joint Staff&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.5 Analyst/ Operations Research&#13;
Operations Research and System Analysis Lead shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Expert in analyzing system solutions to complex and challenging DoD problems. Experience defining operational problems within the fighting forces and using statistical analysis, simulations, predictive modeling, or other methods to analyze it and develop practical solutions.  Experience developing and executing analysis and study plans that address complex problems, examine trade-offs and sensitivities, and produce data and information rich products and artifacts.&#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized mathematics, operations research, statistics, computer science, management science and physics discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 10 years.&#13;
Desired: Masters&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.6 Engineer/Analyst&#13;
Engineer/Analysts shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Experience developing system solutions to complex and challenging DoD problems.   Experience planning and executing complex mission and systems analysis efforts.  Experience conducting systems engineering tasks including Technology Analysis and Assessment, System Definition, Systems Analysis, Systems Architecture development and architecture products, and Logistics support of Department of Defense (DoD) systems.  Expert in assessing threat kill chains operations and identifying exploitable vulnerabilities, analyzing mission threads and blue force system kill chains to identify capability gaps and solutions, developing system models, constructing and executing simulation and analysis plans, conducting trade studies and sensitivity analysis, interpreting and synthesizing results and translating them into concise and comprehensive artifacts for documenting and communicating to multiple audiences. &#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized engineering discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 10 years.&#13;
Desired: Experience interfacing with Joint Staff, Services, and warfighters to coordinate engineering and analysis needs and analytic results.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Non-Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.7 Junior Engineer/Analyst&#13;
Engineer/Analysts shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Experience supporting systems engineering tasks including Technology Analysis and Assessment, System Definition, Systems Analysis, Systems Architecture development and architecture products, kill chain analysis, and Logistics support of Department of Defense (DoD) systems.  Experience supporting assessing threat kill chains operations and identifying exploitable vulnerabilities, analyzing mission threads and blue force system kill chains to identify capability gaps and solutions, developing system models, constructing and executing simulation and analysis plans, conducting trade studies and sensitivity analysis, interpreting and synthesizing results and translating them into concise and comprehensive artifacts for documenting and communicating to multiple audiences. Experience coordinating and integrating engineering activities into concise management level information.&#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized engineering discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 6 years.&#13;
Desired: None.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Non-Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.8 Analyst/Cost Estimator&#13;
Analyst/Cost Estimators shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Expert in developing cost models and cost estimates for the complex DoD weapon systems at multiple levels of fidelity.  Experience with cost estimating aspects of development, acquisition, and operations of DoD weapon systems.  Experience producing cost estimating data and artifacts in support of complex studies examining trade-offs between competing capabilities and various courses of action including formulating constructs for return on investment and metrics used to evaluate system trade-offs and best value options.&#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized engineering, operations research, business administration or equivalent discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 10 years.&#13;
Desired: None.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Non-Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.4.9 Analyst&#13;
Analyst shall serve as functional and technical experts as defined below:&#13;
&#13;
Experience in supporting technical, managerial or operational fields and mature judgement required to interface with external stakeholders and senior government personnel. Strong organizational and oral and written communication skills are required. Experience synthesizing vast amounts of complex technical data into management level information.  Experience preparing presentations and other visualization forms to communicate results and artifacts to varied audiences.  Experience maintaining configuration management on large and complex projects and developing and administering integrated data environments including cloud based storage approaches.&#13;
&#13;
Required: Bachelors in a recognized engineering, operations research, business administration or equivalent discipline that is relevant. Minimum of 5 years.&#13;
Desired: None.&#13;
Clearance: TS/SCI&#13;
Personnel Type: Non-Key &#13;
&#13;
6.7.5 Key Skills and Expertise.&#13;
The contractor shall maintain the ability to access personnel with the following key skills and expertise to execute activates within this task:  &#13;
&#13;
6.7.5.1 Analysts/Engineers with demonstrated experience and capability to:&#13;
1. Structure, design, and manage engagement and campaign level analyses &#13;
2. Digitally model and execute simulations to analyze end-to-end weapon system fire control chains, sensor and communication networks, weapons effects, and Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance system support &#13;
3. Formulate and execute operations research analysis&#13;
4. Estimate materiel solutions and operations cost &#13;
5. Characterize and digitally model threat systems and their effects&#13;
6. Perform analytical computation functions, perform mission, gap, risk, and sensitivity analyses&#13;
&#13;
6.7.5.2 Subject matter expertise in technologies; system capabilities, performance, and operations; and joint force operations, including:&#13;
1. Joint force application and integration, concepts of employment, concepts of operations, and operational constraints&#13;
2. Land, sea, air, and space platforms&#13;
3. Offensive, defensive, kinetic and directed energy weapons from all domains&#13;
4. Sensors for ISR and fire control&#13;
5. Cyberwarfare&#13;
6. Communication networks; &#13;
7. Electromagnetic Spectrum Management &amp;#8211; to include EW and 5G&#13;
8. Automation applications&#13;
9. Command, Control, and Battle Management&#13;
10. Fires &amp;#8211; close air support, long range fires, targeting, air and missile defense&#13;
&#13;
6.8&amp;#9;Substitution of Team Members and Substitution of Personnel&#13;
For Task Orders issued under the Basic Contract, the Contractor agrees to assign to the task order those key persons identified with the Task Order response necessary to fulfill the requirements of the task order. During the first 90 days of performance, the Contractor shall make no substitutions of key personnel unless illness, death, or termination of employment necessitates the substitution. The Contractor shall notify the Contracting Officer Representative and Contracting Officer as soon as possible after the occurrence of any of these events and provide the information required below. No substitution shall be made without prior notification to and concurrence of the COR and CO in accordance with this requirement in writing. &#13;
&#13;
All proposed substitutes shall have qualifications equal to or higher than the qualifications of the person to be replaced. The COR and CO shall be notified in writing of any proposed substitution at least thirty (30) days, or sixty (60) days if a security clearance is to be obtained, in advance of the proposed substitution. Such notification shall include: &#13;
-an explanation of the circumstances necessitating the substitution; &#13;
-a complete resume of the proposed substitute; and &#13;
-any other information requested by the Contracting Officer to enable him/her to judge whether or not the contractor is maintaining the same high quality of personnel that provided the partial basis for award. &#13;
The Contracting Officer will notify the Contractor within 15 calendar days after receipt of all required information of the decision on proposed substitutions.&#13;
&#13;
6.8.1 Conduct. &#13;
Contractor personnel shall present a professional appearance at all times consistent with the usual and customary workforce attire of the assigned Government on-site locations, and their conduct shall not discredit the United States Government. The Government, at its sole discretion, may request the contractor to remove any contractor employee from Government facilities for misconduct, failure to perform, security reasons, or other appropriate reasons that may jeopardize the success of the mission. The Contracting Officer may provide the contractor with a written explanation to support any request to remove an employee.  Removal of contractor personnel does not relieve the contractor of the responsibility to continue providing the services required under this task order. &#13;
&#13;
6.8.2 Non-disclosure Agreements (NDAs). &#13;
The contractor may be required to access Confidential, Proprietary and/or Sensitive Information held by the Government related to the tasks to be performed under this task order. In consideration of the government granting the contractor access to this information, non-disclosure agreements (NDA) shall be required between the contractor and the government.  The terms and conditions are described in detail within the NDA Form document (Attachment 1).  This form shall be signed by all contractor personnel working under this contract and submitted upon TO award to the CO and COR.  The contractor shall ensure that all contractor personnel (including subcontractors) use said information only to meet the requirements of this task order. The contractor (to include subcontractors) shall not disseminate proprietary information or place said information at risk of disclosure unless required and authorized by this task order.  If contractors are replaced during the performance of this contract, then new contractor employees shall sign the NDA Form upon beginning work.&#13;
&#13;
6.8.3 Non-personal Services/Inherently Government Functions. &#13;
All services described in this PWS are non-personal services&amp;#9;, and the contractor shall not perform any inherently government functions.&#13;
&#13;
6.8.4 Data Rights. &#13;
Data Rights are as prescribed in the IDIQ contract FAR/DFARs clauses.&#13;
&#13;
6.9 Telework.&#13;
Contractor employees covered under this TO are authorized to Telework upon receipt of the COR approval. Generally, telework privileges are subject to advance scheduling based on need and required deliverables, with written approval from the COR. The contractor must submit a telework plan identifying the need for telework and the deliverables to be accomplished (e.g. plan of the day), along with a formal agreement, or another form of agreement as requested by the COR.  Contractor employees must comply with criteria and guidelines established by the DoD Chief Information Office and its respective Components for using both GFP and non-GFP and for access to DoD information systems and networks to perform telework.  Telework arrangements may be terminated at the Government&amp;#8217;s discretion. &#13;
&#13;
6.10 On-ramping and Off-ramping.&#13;
The Government may off-ramp contractors, at the CO discretion, if they fail to adequately perform on the TO, get acquired by a non-vetted or large entity, etc. The Government reserves the right to on-ramp new performers when needed.  The exact mechanism is not defined and may be formulated at a later time. The Government may elect to on-ramp a new contractor based on results of the original source selection, to conduct a small competition, or another method at the CO&amp;#8217;s discretion.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 7: DELIVERABLES AND SCHEDULE&#13;
&#13;
All deliverables must meet professional standards and satisfy the requirements set forth in contractual documentation. The Contractor will be responsible for delivering all items specified. All deliverables developed under specific orders become the property of the US Government. The dates by which specific deliverables must be submitted will be as mutually agreed upon between the Government and the Contractor.&#13;
&#13;
Unless otherwise specified, the Government will have a maximum of ten (10) working days from the day the draft deliverable is received to review the document, provide comments back to the Contractor, approve or disapprove the deliverable(s). The Contractor will have a maximum of ten (10) working days from the day comments are received to incorporate all changes and submit the final deliverable to the Government. Contractor trip reports shall summarize the purpose, activities and work performed. All days identified below are intended to be calendar days unless otherwise specified.&#13;
&#13;
The format for individual deliverables will be determined through consultation between the COR and the contractor at the orientation briefing.  Products that reflect the contractor&amp;#8217;s analysis and opinion (e.g., studies or analyses) may be in contractor format. Products that are to be used by the Government project office in the execution of their responsibilities (e.g., strategy documents, reports, roadmaps, analysis and briefings) will be in a specified Government format. All documents will be provided in either hard copy or electronically as requested by the COR. Electronic documents will be provided in the appropriate format (e.g., Word or PowerPoint); if appropriate, the Government may be asked that they be provided in compressed or PDF format.&#13;
&#13;
In fulfillment of this effort, the Contractor shall provide specific deliverables as identified by this Task Order. All deliverables shall be submitted to the COR, and any selected representatives, unless otherwise agreed upon. In addition to the reports listed below, additional reports/products may be requested as deemed necessary:&#13;
&#13;
Management DeliverableFrequency# of CopiesMedium/FormatSubmit ToMission engineering community mapInitial ATP* + 30 days; Updates Monthly1Electronic.  MSWordCORIntegrated mission engineering activity forecastInitial ATP* + 30 days; Updates Monthly1Electronic.  MSWord CORActivity and accomplishment reportWeekly1Electronic.  MSWordCORContractor trip reportsWithin 5 calendar days of travel completion1Electronic.  MSWordCOR&#13;
Per Study DeliverableFrequency# of CopiesMedium/FormatSubmit ToDraft study plan for government approvalStudy Initiation+ 10 days1Electronic.  MSWordCORStudy architecture framework for stakeholder approvalStudy Initiation +30 days1Electronic.  MSWord CORInterim ResultsPer study plan1Electronic.  MSWordCORFinal Study ReportAt completion1Electronic.  MSWordCORDigital tool chain descriptionIntegration of tools, ver # &amp;amp; data flows1Electronic.  MSWordCORResults demonstrationAt interim results report &amp;amp; final report1Electronic.  MSWordCORBriefing PresentationsPer study plan1Electronic.  MSWordCORMission BlueprintDraft per study plan, Final at completion1Electronic.  MSWordCOR*Authorization to Proceed (ATP)&#13;
&#13;
The contractor shall maintain the mission engineering capability over the period of performance.  Within the period of performance, the Contractor shall complete each of the three discrete study tasks within five (5) months.  No more than two (2) individual study tasks will substantially overlap one another at any given time.  The COR shall provide the authorization to proceed and determine the study initiations via email to the contractor Task Order Program Manager (TO PM).  At the COR&amp;#8217;s discretion, the delivery dates may be adjusted. &#13;
&#13;
The format for individual deliverables will be determined through consultation between the COR and the contractor at the Post Award Conference (Section 7.2) and identified in writing then provided to the contracting office, COR, and the contractor.  Products that reflect the contractor&amp;#8217;s analysis and opinion (e.g., studies or analyses) may be in contractor format.  Products that are to be used by the Government in the execution of its responsibilities (e.g., Reports, Briefings) will be in a specified Government format.  All documents will be provided in either hard copy or electronic format, as requested by the COR.  Electronic documents will be provided in the appropriate Microsoft Office format (e.g., Word or PowerPoint); if appropriate, the Contractor may be asked to provide in compressed or Portable Document Format.&#13;
&#13;
At Government request upon contract completion, the Contractor shall transfer all tools, licenses, computer resources, data and artifacts produced or acquired under this contract to the Government.&#13;
&#13;
The contractor shall report ALL contractor labor hours required for performance of services provided under this contract via a secure data collection site. The contractor is required to completely fill in all required data fields using the following web address: https://www.sam.gov/. Reporting inputs will be for the labor executed during the period of performance during each Government fiscal year (FY), which runs October 1 through September 30. While inputs may be reported any time during the FY, all data shall be reported no later than October 31 of each calendar year. Contractors may direct questions to the help desk at help desk at: https://www.sam.gov/.&#13;
&#13;
7.1 Phase in/ Phase out Period.&#13;
In order to minimize any decreases in productivity and to prevent possible negative impacts on additional services, the Contractor shall have personnel on board, during the required phase in/phase out periods.  During the phase in period, the Contractor shall become familiar with performance requirements in order to commence full performance of services on the contract start date.  The COR shall define the phase in/out period(s), as applicable. &#13;
&#13;
7.2 Post Award Conference/Periodic Progress Meetings.  &#13;
The Contractor agrees to attend any post award conference convened by the contracting activity or contract administration office in accordance with Federal Acquisition Regulation Subpart 42.5.  The Contracting Officer, COR, and other Government personnel, as appropriate, may meet periodically with the Contractor to review the Contractor&amp;#39;s performance.  At these meetings, the Contracting Officer will apprise the Contractor of how the Government views the Contractor&amp;#39;s performance and the Contractor will apprise the Government of problems, if any, being experienced.  Appropriate action shall be taken to resolve outstanding issues.  These meetings shall be at no additional cost to the Government.&#13;
&#13;
7.3 Contractor Project Management Plan (CPMP).  &#13;
The CPMP documents the Contractor&amp;#8217;s approach, timeline, and tools to be used in execution of the contract.  The CPMP should take the form of both a narrative and graphic format that displays the schedule, milestones, risks, and resource support.  The CPMP shall also include how the Contractor shall coordinate and execute planned, routine, and ad hoc data requests as identified within the PWS.  The contractor shall develop and maintain an effective quality control program to ensure services are performed in accordance with this PWS.  The contractor shall develop and implement procedures to identify, prevent, and ensure non-recurrence of defective services.  The contractor&amp;#8217;s quality control program is the means by which it assures itself that the work complies with the requirement of the contract.  The initial baseline CPMP shall be provided, concurred upon and finalized within 20 business days after contract award, and updated as needed thereafter, but no less than annually.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 8: PERFORMANCE STANDARDS AND QUALITY MEASUREMENT&#13;
&#13;
8.1&amp;#9;Quality Assurance Surveillance Plan (QASP)&#13;
The Government will use a quality-assurance review process to monitor the contractor&amp;#8217;s performance under this Order. The use of FPAF and CPAF contract types will be utilized when appropriate and Award Fee determinations will leverage the QC, QASP, surveillance thereof, and other control measures instituted at the Task Order level. All order performance, including those not evaluated under the QASP (such as general requirements, Integrated Schedule, Integrated Status Report and the Monthly Reports) will be considered in the requisite annual evaluation of this Contractor&amp;#8217;s performance. &#13;
&#13;
8.1.2 Performance Requirements Summary. &#13;
The Contractor service requirements are summarized into performance objectives that relate directly to mission essential items.  The performance threshold briefly describes the minimum acceptable levels of service required for each requirement.  These thresholds are critical to mission success.&#13;
&#13;
Performance ObjectiveStandardPerformance ThresholdMethod of SurveillancePRS # 1&#13;
The Contractor workforce performs immediately with minimal disturbances and necessary security clearance (or security clearance process started) to support OUSD(R&amp;amp;E) MI.Contractor provides required workforce with adequate security clearance and minimal turbulence during on and off ramping. Contractor begins within 14 calendar days after TO award with appropriate security clearances as defined in the Task Order.  Subsequent vacancies are filled as necessary with minimal disturbance.Validated by COR/Customer observations.PRS # 2&#13;
Contractor workforce consistently generates quality and timely products to support MI.  (See PWS Part 5)Deliverables reflect thorough research in and knowledge of the topic; articulate clear conclusions and/or recommendations, as appropriate; all material is written and formatted as directed; reflects Government guidance on draft; and final material is comprehensive, coherent, accurate, timely, and complete.Accuracy, Appearance, Clarity, Timeliness.  Reports are generated on time and at least (1) week prior to decision meeting.  Reports are accurate.  No more than one (1) customer complaint per report.Validated by COR/Customer observations.PRS # 3&#13;
Contractor workforce reviews and generates quality and timely assessments of policy, documents, and other artifacts related to support MI (See PWS Part 5).All support, activities, and initiatives reflect thorough research in and knowledge of the topic; articulate clear conclusions and/or recommendations, as appropriate; all material is written and formatted as directed; reflects Government guidance on draft, and final material is comprehensive, coherent, accurate, timely, and complete.Accuracy, Appearance, Clarity, Timeliness.  Analysis is complete and report is generated on time at least (1) week prior to suspense.  Documents are accurate.  No more than one (1) customer complaint per report.Validated by COR/Customer observations.&#13;
8.2&amp;#9;Quality Control (QC)&#13;
The Contractor shall institute a complete QC Program to ensure that the requirements of this contract are fulfilled as specified. At a minimum, the Contractor shall include the following elements in the program:&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;A comprehensive inspection system of all scheduled and unscheduled services required in this document.&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;Name and contact information of designated QC Inspector and backup performing inspections.&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;A proactive methodology to identify and correct problems before the Government identifies these problems. Contractor shall notify the Government of any problems.&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;An organized, current file of all Contractor conducted inspections, corrective actions taken, and follow-up inspections.&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;How projects will be managed to minimize layers of management and oversight, while still providing for accountability.&#13;
&amp;#183;&amp;#9;How the order will be managed to provide for clear communications between the contractor, Government program office, and Ordering Contracting Office.&#13;
&#13;
8.3&amp;#9;Organizational Conflicts of Interest (OCI).&#13;
Contractor and subcontractor personnel performing work under this contract may receive, have access to or participate in the development of proprietary or source selection information (e.g., cost or pricing information, budget information or analyses, specifications or work statements, etc.) or perform evaluation services which may create a current or subsequent Organizational Conflict of Interests (OCI) as defined in FAR Subpart 9.5.  The Contractor shall notify the Contracting Officer immediately whenever it becomes aware that such access or participation may result in any actual or potential OCI and shall promptly submit a plan to the Contracting Officer to avoid or mitigate any such OCI.  The Contractor&amp;#8217;s mitigation plan will be determined to be acceptable solely at the discretion of the Contracting Officer and in the event the Contracting Officer unilaterally determines that any such OCI cannot be satisfactorily avoided or mitigated, the Contracting Officer may affect other remedies as deemed necessary, including prohibiting the Contractor from participation in subsequent contracted requirements which may be affected by the OCI.  The OCI Form found in Attachment 2 shall be completed by the contractor and submitted with the proposal.  Reference Section 8.3 OCI on the IDIQ contract for further details. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 9: Applicable Publications (Current Editions)&#13;
&#13;
9.1&amp;#9;The Contractor must abide by all applicable regulations, publications, manuals, and local policies and procedures including the following:  none at this time. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Part 10: ATTACHMENT/TECHNICAL EXHIBIT&#13;
&#13;
10.&amp;#9;Attachment/Technical Exhibit List.&#13;
10.1&amp;#9;Attachment 1/Non-Disclosure Agreement Form&#13;
10.2&amp;#9;Attachment 2/Organizational Conflict of Interest Form&#13;
10.3 Attachment 3/DD254 Form &amp;#8220;Department of Defense Contract Security Classification Specification&amp;#8221;&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Attachment 1&#13;
&#13;
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT&#13;
&amp;#9;This Non-Disclosure Agreement is by and between [NAME] and the Office of Under Secretary of Defense for Research and Engineering (OUSD R&amp;amp;E).&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
I, [NAME], (hereinafter RECIPIENT), an employee of [COMPANY NAME], a Contractor providing support to the Office of Under Secretary of Defense for Research and Engineering (OUSD R&amp;amp;E) ( hereinafter OUSD R&amp;amp;E or Government) and likely to have access to nonpublic information, agree to and promise the following:&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;WHEREAS RECIPIENT is engaged in delivering support services to OUSD R&amp;amp;E under [CONTRACT NUMBER]; and&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;WHEREAS it is the intention of OUSD R&amp;amp;E to protect and prevent access to and disclosure of nonpublic information, including but not limited to non-public Government Furnished Information as well as other contractor information including technical and potentially sensitive and proprietary data and materials applicable to [ENTER INITIATIVE TITLE] information, to anyone other than employees of the United States Government and others who have a need to know, unless so authorized by the Contracting Officer&amp;#39;s Representative; and&#13;
&#13;
WHEREAS OUSD R&amp;amp;D warrants that it has the right to disclose Proprietary Information hereunder for the purpose of performance under [CONTRACT NUMBER]; and &#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;WHEREAS OUSD R&amp;amp;E acknowledges that RECIPIENT will have or require access to such nonpublic information in the course of delivering the contract services; and therefore,&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;WHEREAS RECIPIENT will be given or otherwise have access to nonpublic information while providing such services; and finally,&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;WHEREAS &amp;quot;nonpublic information&amp;quot; includes such information as classified information, Government Furnished Information, trade secrets and other confidential business information (e.g., confidential business information submitted by a contractor), information protected by the Privacy Act, and other sensitive information that would not be released by OUSD R&amp;amp;E under the Freedom of Information Act;&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;NOW THEREFORE, RECIPIENT agrees to and promises as follows:&#13;
&#13;
This agreement is effective as of the date of signature below.&#13;
&#13;
The term of this agreement is the period of performance of contract [CONTRACT NUMBER]&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#8220;Choice of Law&amp;#8221; shall mean the laws of the State of Delaware or the applicable law as determined by a court of competent jurisdiction.&#13;
RECIPIENT shall hold information in confidentiality upon disclosure of Proprietary Information hereunder, and expire five (5)  years after the termination or expiration of this Agreement, or any extension(s) thereof.&#13;
U.S.G. classified information, if any, disclosed under this agreement shall be handled in accordance with the National Industrial Security Program Operating Manual (NISPOM), their supplements, and other applicable U.S.G. security regulations.&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;RECIPIENT shall not seek access to nonpublic information beyond what is required for the performance of the support services contract;&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;RECIPIENT will ensure that his or her status as a contractor employee is known when seeking access to and receiving such nonpublic information from Government employees;&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;As to any nonpublic information to which RECIPIENT has or is given access, RECIPIENT shall not use or disclose such information for any purpose other than providing the contract support services, and will not use or disclose the information for any personal or other commercial purpose; and&#13;
&#13;
RECIPIENT agrees to use a high degree of reasonable care in safeguarding Nonpublic information, including but not limited to reasonable safeguards to protect Nonpublic Information from unauthorized disclosure, access, or use, regardless of whether such information is in paper, electronic, or other form.&#13;
&#13;
If RECIPIENT becomes aware of any improper release or disclosure of such nonpublic information, RECIPIENT will advise the Contracting Officer&amp;#39;s Representative in writing as soon as possible. &#13;
&#13;
RECIPIENT shall not be liable hereunder for use or disclosure of Nonpublic Information which:  &#13;
a.&amp;#9;is or becomes publicly known through no wrongful act of RECIPIENT; or&#13;
b.&amp;#9;is already known to or in the possession of RECIPIENT prior to the disclosure thereof by OUSD R&amp;amp;E, as evidenced by competent proof; or&#13;
c.&amp;#9;is rightfully received by RECIPIENT from a third party without restriction and without breach of this Agreement; or&#13;
d.&amp;#9;is independently developed by Recipient without the use of the Nonpublic Information; or&#13;
e.&amp;#9;is used or disclosed after the expiration of the Confidentiality Period; or&#13;
f.&amp;#9;is disclosed to satisfy a legal order by a court of competent jurisdiction or U.S. Governmental action; provided, however, that the RECIPIENT shall first advise OUSD R&amp;amp;E within sufficient time prior to the disclosure so that OUSD R&amp;amp;E has the opportunity to seek appropriate relief from the court or Governmental order, and provided further that RECIPIENT shall disclose only those portions of the Nonpublic Information which is legally required to be disclosed and request confidential treatment of the Nonpublic Information by the court or Governmental entity.&#13;
&amp;#9;The RECIPIENT agrees to return any nonpublic information given to him or her pursuant to this agreement, including any transcriptions by RECIPIENT of nonpublic information to which RECIPIENT was given access, if not already destroyed, upon RECIPIENT leaving the contract.&#13;
&#13;
RECIPIENT may retain a single archival copy of the received nonpublic information which may be used solely for legal evidentiary purposes in the event of a dispute arising under this Agreement.&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#9;RECIPIENT understands that any unauthorized use, release or disclosure of nonpublic information in violation of this Agreement will subject the RECIPIENT to administrative, civil or criminal remedies, as may be authorized by law.&#13;
&#13;
Defend Trade Secrets Act.&amp;#160; Pursuant to the Defend Trade Secrets Act of 2016, if RECIPIENT is an individual, RECIPIENT acknowledges that he/she shall not have criminal or civil liability under any Federal or State trade secret law for the disclosure of a trade secret that (A) is made (i) in confidence to a Federal, State, or local government official, either directly or indirectly, or to an attorney and (ii) solely for the purpose of reporting or investigating a suspected violation of law; or (B) is made in a complaint or other document filed in a lawsuit or other proceeding, if such filing is made under seal. &#13;
&#13;
****These provisions are consistent with and do not supersede, conflict with, or otherwise alter the employee obligations, rights, or liabilities created by existing statute or Executive order relating to (1) classified information, (2) communications to Congress, (3) the reporting to an Inspector General of a violation of any law, rule, or regulation, or mismanagement, a gross waste of funds, an abuse of authority, or a substantial and specific danger to public health or safety, or (4) any other whistleblower protection.  The definitions, requirements, obligations, rights, sanctions, and liabilities created by controlling Executive orders and statutory provisions are incorporated into this agreement and are controlling.****&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
__________________________________________________________&#13;
SIGNATURE AND DATE&#13;
&#13;
PRINTED NAME: _____&#13;
&#13;
TITLE:  ______________&#13;
&#13;
EMPLOYER:  ____ _____&#13;
&#13;
AGREEMENT REFERENCE:___________________________________________&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Attachment 2&#13;
&#13;
OCI ANALYSIS/ DISCLOSURE FORM&#13;
1. Task Order Number&#13;
2. Program Title&#13;
3. Contractor Name and Address&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
4. Telephone Number and POC&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
5. Type of work to be performed under this agreement:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Other Professional Services - related work requiring analysis and determination:6. Contract Number and Program Title&#13;
&#13;
7. Brief Summary/ Description of work performed under Block 6 action:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
8. Relationship between requirements of Block 1 action and work performed under Block 6 action (If None, State Why):&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
9. Offeror/Contractor OCI Evaluation and Assessment (If either answer is yes, attach a copy of the SOW and complete Block 10):&#13;
&#13;
(a)&amp;#9;Does Actual OCI exist?  (  ) Yes  (  ) No&#13;
(b)&amp;#9;Does Potential OCI exist? (  ) Yes  (  ) No&#13;
10. Summary of actual/potential OCI, including actions planned to avoid, neutralize, or mitigate conflict or potential conflict:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
11. Typed Name of Responsible Official&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
12. Signature&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
13. Date&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
14. Typed Name of Contracting Officer&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
15. Approval Signature&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
16. Date&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
INSTRUCTIONS FOR COMPLETING OCI ANALYSIS/ DISCLOSURE FORM&#13;
&#13;
Blocks 1 through 5:  Self explanatory&#13;
&#13;
Block 6:  Fill in the number and the short, official title by which the contract or subcontract requiring analysis and determination is formally known.  This is work that has already been awarded, is being performed by your company, and requires a comparison with the work described in Blocks 1 &amp;#8211; 5.  NOTE:  One OCI Analysis/ Disclosure Form shall be submitted for EACH related contract or subcontract currently being performed.&#13;
&#13;
Block 7:  Provide a brief, but specific, narrative summary of the SOW and work performed on the contract or subcontract listed in Block 6, including the period of performance and the value.&#13;
&#13;
Block 8:  Provide a brief, but specific, narrative summary of ANY relationship between the work to be performed under the action listed in Block 1 and the previous work performed under the action listed in Block 6.  Please be as specific as possible by citing the specific RFP/SOW paragraph where possible.&#13;
&#13;
Block 9: Place an &amp;#8220;X&amp;#8221; in the appropriate (  ) for your responses.&#13;
&#13;
Block 10:  If you answer yes to either 9(a) or to 9(b), provide a summary of the actual or potential OCI.&#13;
&#13;
Blocks 11, 12, and 13:  Provide the name of your company official with the responsibility for and/or authority to discuss and commit the company on matters related to OCI issues.  That official should then sign and date each form.&#13;
&#13;
Attachment 3&#13;
&#13;
Reference the RETS IDIQ DD254.  &#13;
&#13;
&lt;/MiscellaneousText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;C&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/MiscellaneousTextDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;MiscellaneousTextDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;MiscellaneousText&gt;Contract Clauses&#13;
I&#13;
252.201-9000 WHS/AD LOCAL CLAUSE: CONTRACTING OFFICER&amp;#8217;S REPRESENTATIVE (COR) (MAR 2015) &#13;
&#13;
(a) The Contracting Officer&amp;#8217;s Representative (COR) is a representative of the Government with limited authority who has been designated in writing by the Contracting Officer to provide technical direction, clarification, and guidance with respect to existing specifications and performance work statement/statement of work/statement of objectives, as established in the contract. The COR also monitors the progress and quality of the Contractor&amp;#8217;s performance for payment purposes. The COR shall promptly report Contractor performance discrepancies and suggested corrective actions to the Contracting Officer for resolution. &#13;
&#13;
(b) The COR is not authorized to take any direct or indirect actions or make any commitments that will result in changes to price, quantity, quality, schedule, place of performance, delivery or any other terms or conditions of the written contract. &#13;
&#13;
(c) The Contractor is responsible for promptly providing written notification to the Contracting Officer if it believes the COR has requested or directed any change to the existing contract. No action shall be taken by the Contractor for any proposed change to the existing contract. No action shall be taken by the Contractor for any proposed change to the contract until the Contracting Officer has issued a written directive or a written modification to the contract. The Government will not accept and is not liable for any alleged change to the contract unless the change is included in a written contract modification or directive signed by the Contracting Officer. &#13;
&#13;
(d) COR authority is not delegable. &#13;
(e) The COR for this contract is: Marc Goldenberg, 571-239-7327/703-692-6551, marc.j.goldenberg.civ@mail.mil&#13;
(end of clause)&#13;
&#13;
Contract Clauses&#13;
IDIQ FLOWDOWN&#13;
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE IDIQ AWARD SECTION H.1, THE BASIC CONTRACT IS INCORPORATED IN ITS ENTIRETY IN THIS TASK ORDER.&#13;
&lt;/MiscellaneousText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/MiscellaneousTextDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;NotFullOpenCompetition&gt;None&lt;/NotFullOpenCompetition&gt;&#13;
                &lt;PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;PricingArrangementBase&gt;Firm Fixed Price&lt;/PricingArrangementBase&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                &lt;SolicitationOfferInformation&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;NAICSCode&gt;541715&lt;/NAICSCode&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/SolicitationOfferInformation&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/BasicInformation&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ClauseInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;RegulationURL&gt;http://www.arnet.gov&lt;/RegulationURL&gt;&#13;
                &lt;RegulationURL&gt;http://www.acq.osd.mil/dpap/dars/index.html&lt;/RegulationURL&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;DFARS&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;252.232-7006&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Wide Area WorkFlow Payment Instructions&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;2018-12&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;252.232-7006 WIDE AREA WORKFLOW PAYMENT INSTRUCTIONS (DEC 2018)&#13;
 &#13;
&#13;
(a) Definitions. As used in this clause&amp;#8212;&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#8220;Department of Defense Activity Address Code (DoDAAC)&amp;#8221; is a six position code that uniquely identifies a unit, activity, or organization.&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#8220;Document type&amp;#8221; means the type of payment request or receiving report available for creation in Wide Area WorkFlow (WAWF).&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#8220;Local processing office (LPO)&amp;#8221; is the office responsible for payment certification when payment certification is done external to the entitlement system.&#13;
&#13;
&amp;#8220;Payment request&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;receiving report&amp;#8221; are defined in the clause at 252.232-7003, Electronic Submission of Payment Requests and Receiving Reports.&#13;
&#13;
(b) Electronic invoicing. The WAWF system provides the method to electronically process vendor payment requests and receiving reports, as authorized by Defense Federal Acquisition Regulation Supplement (DFARS) 252.232-7003, Electronic Submission of Payment Requests and Receiving Reports.&#13;
&#13;
(c) WAWF access. To access WAWF, the Contractor shall&amp;#8212;&#13;
&#13;
(1) Have a designated electronic business point of contact in the System for Award Management at https://www.sam.gov; and&#13;
&#13;
(2) Be registered to use WAWF at https://wawf.eb.mil/ following the step-by-step procedures for self-registration available at this web site.&#13;
&#13;
(d) WAWF training. The Contractor should follow the training instructions of the WAWF Web-Based Training Course and use the Practice Training Site before submitting payment requests through WAWF. Both can be accessed by selecting the &amp;#8220;Web Based Training&amp;#8221; link on the WAWF home page at https://wawf.eb.mil/.&#13;
&#13;
(e) WAWF methods of document submission. Document submissions may be via web entry, Electronic Data Interchange, or File Transfer Protocol.&#13;
&#13;
(f) WAWF payment instructions. The Contractor shall use the following information when submitting payment requests and receiving reports in WAWF for this contract or task or delivery order:&#13;
&#13;
(1)  Document type. The Contractor shall submit payment requests using the following document type(s):&#13;
&#13;
(i) For cost-type line items, including labor-hour or time-and-materials, submit a cost voucher.&#13;
&#13;
(ii) For fixed price line items&amp;#8212;&#13;
&#13;
(A) That require shipment of a deliverable, submit the invoice and receiving report specified by the Contracting Officer.&#13;
&#13;
See the COR for instructions.&#13;
&#13;
(B) For services that do not require shipment of a deliverable, submit either the Invoice 2in1, which meets the requirements for the invoice and receiving report, or the applicable invoice and receiving report, as specified by the Contracting Officer.&#13;
&#13;
Invoice 2in1 &#13;
&#13;
(iii) For customary progress payments based on costs incurred, submit a progress payment request.&#13;
&#13;
(iv) For performance based payments, submit a performance based payment request.&#13;
&#13;
(v) For commercial item financing, submit a commercial item financing request.&#13;
&#13;
(2) Fast Pay requests are only permitted when Federal Acquisition Regulation (FAR) 52.213-1 is included in the contract.&#13;
&#13;
[Note: The Contractor may use a WAWF &amp;#8220;combo&amp;#8221; document type to create some combinations of invoice and receiving report in one step.]&#13;
&#13;
(3) Document routing. The Contractor shall use the information in the Routing Data Table below only to fill in applicable fields in WAWF when creating payment requests and receiving reports in the system.&#13;
Routing Data Table*&#13;
Field Name in WAWFData to be entered in WAWF Pay Official DoDAAC&amp;#160;HQ0768Issue By DoDAAC&amp;#160;HQ0034Admin DoDAAC**&amp;#160;HQ0034Inspect By DoDAAC&amp;#160;Not applicableShip To Code&amp;#160;Not applicableShip From Code&amp;#160;Not applicableMark For Code&amp;#160;Not applicableService Approver (DoDAAC)&amp;#160;Not applicableService Acceptor (DoDAAC)&amp;#160;HQ0287Accept at Other DoDAAC&amp;#160;Not applicableLPO DoDAAC&amp;#160;Not applicableDCAA Auditor DoDAACNot applicableOther DoDAAC(s)Not applicable(4) Payment request. The Contractor shall ensure a payment request includes documentation appropriate to the type of payment request in accordance with the payment clause, contract financing clause, or Federal Acquisition Regulation 52.216-7, Allowable Cost and Payment, as applicable.&#13;
(5) Receiving report. The Contractor shall ensure a receiving report meets the requirements of DFARS Appendix F.&#13;
(g) WAWF point of contact.&#13;
(1) The Contractor may obtain clarification regarding invoicing in WAWF from the following contracting activity&amp;#8217;s WAWF point of contact.&#13;
Contracting Officer: Elaine Wong, 703-835-6679, elaine.d.wong.civ@mail.mil&#13;
Contracting Officer&amp;#8217;s Representative: Marc Goldenberg, 571-239-7327/703-692-6551, marc.j.goldenberg.civ@mail.mil&#13;
(2) Contact the WAWF helpdesk at 866-618-5988, if assistance is needed.&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;DFARS&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;252.232-7007&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Limitation Of Government&amp;#39;s Obligation&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;2014-04&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;252.232-7007      LIMITATION OF GOVERNMENT&amp;#39;S OBLIGATION (APR 2014)&#13;
&#13;
(a) Contract line item(s) 0001 is incrementally funded. For this item, the sum of $4,614,250.00 of &#13;
the total price is presently available for payment and allotted to this contract. An allotment schedule is set forth in paragraph (j) of this clause.&#13;
&#13;
(b)  For items(s) identified in paragraph (a) of this clause, the Contractor agrees to perform up to the point at which the total amount payable by the Government, including reimbursement in the event of termination of those item(s) for the Government&amp;#39;s convenience, approximates the total amount currently allotted to the contract.  The Contractor is not authorized to continue work on those item(s) beyond that point. The Government will not be obligated in any event to reimburse the Contractor in excess of the amount allotted to the contract for those item(s) regardless of anything to the contrary in the clause entitled &amp;quot;TERMINATION FOR THE CONVENIENCE OF THE GOVERNMENT.&amp;quot;  As used in this clause, the total amount payable by the Government in the event of termination of applicable contract line item(s) for convenience includes costs, profit and estimated termination settlement costs for those item(s).&#13;
&#13;
(c)  Notwithstanding the dates specified in the allotment schedule in paragraph (j) of this clause, the Contractor will notify the Contracting Officer in writing at least  ninety days prior to the date when, in the Contractor&amp;#39;s best judgment, the work will reach the point at which the total amount payable by the Government, including any cost for termination for convenience, will approximate 85 percent of the total amount then allotted to the contract for performance of the applicable item(s).  The notification will state (1) the estimated date when that point will be reached and (2) an estimate of additional funding, if any, needed to continue performance of applicable line items up to the next scheduled date for allotment of funds identified in paragraph (j) of this clause, or to a mutually agreed upon substitute date.  The notification will also advise the Contracting Officer of the estimated amount of additional funds that will be required for the timely performance of the item(s) funded pursuant to this clause, for subsequent period as may be specified in the allotment schedule in paragraph (j) of this clause, or otherwise agreed to by the parties.  If after such notification additional funds are not allotted by the date identified in the Contractor&amp;#39;s notification, or by an agreed substitute date, the Contracting Officer will terminate any item(s) for which additional funds have not been allotted, pursuant to the clause of this contract entitled &amp;quot;TERMINATION FOR THE CONVENIENCE OF THE GOVERNMENT&amp;quot;.&#13;
&#13;
(d)  When additional funds are allotted for continued performance of the contract line item(s) identified in paragraph (a) of this clause, the parties will agree as to the period of contract performance which will be covered by the funds.  The provisions of paragraph (b) through (d) of this clause will apply in like manner to the additional allotted funds and agreed substitute date, and the contract will be modified accordingly.&#13;
&#13;
(e)  If, solely by reason of failure of the Government to allot additional funds, by the dates indicated below, in amounts sufficient for timely performance of the contract line item(s) identified in paragraph (a) of this clause, the Contractor incurs additional costs or is delayed in the performance of the work under this contract and if additional funds are allotted, an equitable adjustment will be made in the price or prices (including appropriate target, billing, and ceiling prices where applicable) of the item(s), or in the time of delivery, or both.  Failure to agree to any such equitable adjustment hereunder will be a dispute concerning a question of fact within the meaning of the clause entitled &amp;quot;disputes.&amp;quot;&#13;
&#13;
(f)  The Government may at any time prior to termination allot additional funds for the performance of the contract line item(s) identified in paragraph (a) of this clause.&#13;
&#13;
(g)  The termination provisions of this clause do not limit the rights of the Government under the clause entitled &amp;quot;DEFAULT.&amp;quot;  The provisions of this clause are limited to work and allotment of funds for the contract line item(s) set forth in paragraph (a) of this clause.  This clause no longer applies once the contract if fully funded except with regard to the rights or obligations of the parties concerning equitable adjustments negotiated under paragraphs (d) or (e) of this clause.&#13;
&#13;
(h)  Nothing in this clause affects the right of the Government to this contract pursuant to the clause of this contract entitled &amp;quot;TERMINATION FOR CONVENIENCE OF THE GOVERNMENT.&amp;quot;&#13;
&#13;
(i) Nothing in this clause shall be construed as authorization of voluntary services whose acceptance is otherwise prohibited under 31 U.S.C. 1342.&#13;
&#13;
(j) The parties contemplate that the Government will allot funds to this contract in accordance with the following schedule:&#13;
&#13;
On execution of contract $4,700,000.00&#13;
&#13;
February 28, 2020 $2,238,986.60 (remaining balance)&#13;
&#13;
Total obligation $6,938,986.60&#13;
&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;DFARS&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;252.204-7006&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Billing Instructions&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;2005-10&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;252.204-7006   BILLING INSTRUCTIONS (OCT 2005)&#13;
&#13;
When submitting a request for payment, the Contractor shall--&#13;
&#13;
(a) Identify the contract line item(s) on the payment request that reasonably reflect contract work performance; and&#13;
&#13;
(b) Separately identify a payment amount for each contract line item included in the payment request.&#13;
&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;DFARS&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;252.231-7000&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Supplemental Cost Principles&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;1991-12&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;252.231-7000     SUPPLEMENTAL COST PRINCIPLES (DEC 1991)&#13;
 &#13;
When the allowability of costs under this contract is determined in accordance with part 31 of the Federal Acquisition Regulation (FAR), allowability shall also be determined in accordance with part 231 of the Defense FAR Supplement, in effect on the date of this contract.&#13;
&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;FAR&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;52.217-8&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Option To Extend Services&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;1999-11&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;52.217-8     OPTION TO EXTEND SERVICES (NOV 1999)&#13;
&#13;
The Government may require continued performance of any services within the limits and at the rates specified in the contract.  These rates may be adjusted only as a result of revisions to prevailing labor rates provided by the Secretary of Labor.  The option provision may be exercised more than once, but the total extension of performance hereunder shall not exceed 6 months.  The Contracting Officer may exercise the option by written notice to the Contractor within 30 days from performance expiration.&#13;
&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;RegulationOrSupplement&gt;FAR&lt;/RegulationOrSupplement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseNumber&gt;52.204-25&lt;/ClauseNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseTitle&gt;Prohibition on Contracting for Certain Telecommunications and Video Surveillance Services or Equipment.&lt;/ClauseTitle&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;2020-08&lt;/ClauseEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ClauseFullText&gt;52.204-25  Prohibition on Contracting for Certain Telecommunications and Video Surveillance Services or Equipment (AUG 2020)&#13;
&#13;
(a) Definitions. As used in this clause--&#13;
    &#13;
Backhaul means intermediate links between the core network, or backbone network, and the small subnetworks at the edge of the network (e.g., connecting cell phones/towers to the core telephone network). Backhaul can be wireless (e.g., microwave) or wired (e.g., fiber optic, coaxial cable, Ethernet).&#13;
&#13;
Covered foreign country means The People&amp;#39;s Republic of China.&#13;
    &#13;
Covered telecommunications equipment or services means--&#13;
    &#13;
(1) Telecommunications equipment produced by Huawei Technologies Company or ZTE Corporation (or any subsidiary or affiliate of such entities);&#13;
    &#13;
(2) For the purpose of public safety, security of Government facilities, physical security surveillance of critical &#13;
infrastructure, and other national security purposes, video surveillance and telecommunications equipment produced by Hytera Communications Corporation, Hangzhou Hikvision Digital Technology Company, or Dahua Technology Company (or any subsidiary or affiliate of such entities);&#13;
    &#13;
(3) Telecommunications or video surveillance services provided by such entities or using such equipment; or&#13;
    &#13;
(4) Telecommunications or video surveillance equipment or services produced or provided by an entity that the Secretary of Defense, in consultation with the Director of National Intelligence or the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation, reasonably believes to be an entity owned or controlled by, or otherwise connected to, the government of a covered foreign country.&#13;
    &#13;
Critical technology means--&#13;
    &#13;
(1) Defense articles or defense services included on the United States Munitions List set forth in the International Traffic in Arms Regulations under subchapter M of chapter I of title 22, Code of Federal Regulations;&#13;
    &#13;
(2) Items included on the Commerce Control List set forth in Supplement No. 1 to part 774 of the Export Administration Regulations under subchapter C of chapter VII of title 15, Code of Federal Regulations, and controlled--&#13;
    &#13;
(i) Pursuant to multilateral regimes, including for reasons relating to national security, chemical and biological weapons proliferation, nuclear nonproliferation, or missile technology; or&#13;
    &#13;
(ii) For reasons relating to regional stability or surreptitious listening;&#13;
    &#13;
(3) Specially designed and prepared nuclear equipment, parts and components, materials, software, and technology covered by part 810 of title 10, Code of Federal Regulations (relating to assistance to foreign atomic energy activities);&#13;
    &#13;
(4) Nuclear facilities, equipment, and material covered by part 110 of title 10, Code of Federal Regulations (relating to export and import of nuclear equipment and material);&#13;
    &#13;
(5) Select agents and toxins covered by part 331 of title 7, Code of Federal Regulations, part 121 of title 9 of such Code, or part 73 of title 42 of such Code; or&#13;
    &#13;
(6) Emerging and foundational technologies controlled pursuant to section 1758 of the Export Control Reform Act of 2018 (50 U.S.C. 4817).&#13;
    &#13;
Interconnection arrangements means arrangements governing the physical connection of two or more networks to allow the use of another&amp;#39;s network to hand off traffic where it is ultimately delivered (e.g., connection of a customer of telephone provider A to a customer of telephone company B) or sharing data and other information resources.&#13;
&#13;
Reasonable inquiry means an inquiry designed to uncover any information in the entity&amp;#39;s possession about the identity of the producer or provider of covered telecommunications equipment or services used by the entity that excludes the need to include an internal or third-party audit.&#13;
&#13;
Roaming means cellular communications services (e.g., voice, video, data) received from a visited network when unable to connect to the facilities of the home network either because signal coverage is too weak or because traffic is too high.&#13;
&#13;
Substantial or essential component means any component necessary for the proper function or performance of a piece of equipment, system, or service.&#13;
    &#13;
(b) Prohibition. &#13;
&#13;
(1) Section 889(a)(1)(A) of the John S. McCain National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2019 (Pub. L. 115-232) prohibits the head of an executive agency on or after August 13, 2019, from procuring or obtaining, or extending or renewing a contract to procure or obtain, any equipment, system, or service that uses covered telecommunications equipment or services as a substantial or essential component of any system, or as critical technology as part of any system. The Contractor is prohibited from providing to the Government any equipment, system, or service that uses covered telecommunications equipment or services as a substantial or essential component of any system, or as critical technology as part of any system, unless an exception at paragraph (c) of this clause applies or the covered telecommunication equipment or services are covered by a waiver described in FAR 4.2104.&#13;
&#13;
(2) Section 889(a)(1)(B) of the John S. McCain National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2019 (Pub. L. 115-232) prohibits the head of an executive agency on or after August 13, 2020, from entering into a contract, or extending or renewing a contract, with an entity that uses any equipment, system, or service that uses covered telecommunications equipment or services as a substantial or essential component of any system, or as critical technology as part of any system, unless an exception at paragraph (c) of this clause applies or the covered telecommunication equipment or services are covered by a waiver described in FAR 4.2104. This prohibition applies to the use of covered telecommunications equipment or services, regardless of whether that use is in performance of work under a Federal contract.&#13;
    &#13;
(c) Exceptions. This clause does not prohibit contractors from providing--&#13;
    &#13;
(1) A service that connects to the facilities of a third-party, such as backhaul, roaming, or interconnection arrangements; or&#13;
    &#13;
(2) Telecommunications equipment that cannot route or redirect user data traffic or permit visibility into any user data or packets that such equipment transmits or otherwise handles.&#13;
    &#13;
(d) Reporting requirement. &#13;
&#13;
(1) In the event the Contractor identifies covered telecommunications equipment or services used as a substantial or essential component of any system, or as critical technology as part of any system, during contract performance, or the Contractor is notified of such by a subcontractor at any tier or by any other source, the Contractor shall report the information in paragraph (d)(2) of this clause to the Contracting Officer, unless elsewhere in this contract are established procedures for reporting the information; in the case of the Department of Defense, the Contractor shall report to the website at https://dibnet.dod.mil. For indefinite delivery contracts, the Contractor shall report to the Contracting Officer for the indefinite delivery contract and the Contracting Officer(s) for any affected order or, in the case of the Department of Defense, identify both the indefinite delivery contract and any affected orders in the report provided at https://dibnet.dod.mil.&#13;
    &#13;
(2) The Contractor shall report the following information pursuant to paragraph (d)(1) of this clause:&#13;
    &#13;
(i) Within one business day from the date of such identification or notification: The contract number; the order number(s), if applicable; supplier name; supplier unique entity identifier (if known); supplier Commercial and Government Entity (CAGE) code (if known); brand; model number (original equipment manufacturer number, &#13;
manufacturer part number, or wholesaler number); item description; and any readily available information about mitigation actions undertaken or recommended.&#13;
    &#13;
(ii) Within 10 business days of submitting the information in paragraph (d)(2)(i) of this clause: Any further available &#13;
information about mitigation actions undertaken or recommended. In addition, the Contractor shall describe the efforts it undertook to prevent use or submission of covered telecommunications equipment or services, and any additional efforts that will be incorporated to prevent future use or submission of covered telecommunications &#13;
equipment or services.&#13;
    &#13;
(e) Subcontracts. The Contractor shall insert the substance of this clause, including this paragraph (e) and excluding paragraph (b)(2), in all subcontracts and other contractual instruments, including subcontracts for the acquisition of commercial items.&#13;
&#13;
(End of clause)&#13;
&#13;
&lt;/ClauseFullText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ClauseText&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;I&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ClauseDetails&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ClauseInformation&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentDates&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentEffectiveDate&gt;2020-11-25&lt;/ProcurementInstrumentEffectiveDate&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ProcurementInstrumentPeriods&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;PeriodDescription&gt;Period of Performance&lt;/PeriodDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;StartDate&gt;2020-12-01&lt;/StartDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;EndDate&gt;2021-11-30&lt;/EndDate&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentPeriods&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ContractingOfficer&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;SignatureDate&gt;2020-11-25&lt;/SignatureDate&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;SigneeDetails&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;TitleOrFunction&gt;CONTRACTING OFFICER&lt;/TitleOrFunction&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Name&gt;ELAINE D. WONG&lt;/Name&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OfficeCode&gt;HQ0034&lt;/OfficeCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Telephone&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;MethodValue&gt;703-545-3357&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Email&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;MethodValue&gt;elaine.d.wong.civ@mail.mil&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/SigneeDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ContractingOfficer&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentDates&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Contract Administrative Office&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0034&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS - ACQUISITION DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;4800 MARK CENTER DRIVE, SUITE 09F09&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;ALEXANDRIA, VA 22350&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Contract Issuing Office&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0034&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS - ACQUISITION DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;4800 MARK CENTER DRIVE, SUITE 09F09&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;ALEXANDRIA, VA 22350&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Paying Office&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0768&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;1155 DEFENSE PENTAGON&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;WASHINGTON, DC 20301-1155&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Place of Performance&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Cage&gt;0X988&lt;/Cage&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DunsNumber&gt;807454640&lt;/DunsNumber&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;Modern Technology Solutions, Inc.&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;5285 Shawnee Rd Ste 400&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;Alexandria, VA 22312-2328&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Remit To&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Cage&gt;0X988&lt;/Cage&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DunsNumber&gt;807454640&lt;/DunsNumber&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;Modern Technology Solutions, Inc.&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;5285 Shawnee Rd Ste 400&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;Alexandria, VA 22312-2328&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Contact&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;TitleOrFunction&gt;CONTRACTS MANAGER&lt;/TitleOrFunction&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Name&gt;SHELLY BURTON&lt;/Name&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Telephone&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodValue&gt;937-490-3437&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Email&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodValue&gt;shelly.burton@mtsi-va.com&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Contact&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Contractor&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Cage&gt;0X988&lt;/Cage&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DunsNumber&gt;807454640&lt;/DunsNumber&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;Microsoft Corporation&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;5285 Shawnee Rd Ste 400&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;Alexandria, VA 22312-2328&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Contact&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;TitleOrFunction&gt;CONTRACTS MANAGER&lt;/TitleOrFunction&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Name&gt;SHELLY BURTON&lt;/Name&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Telephone&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodValue&gt;937-490-3437&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Email&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;MethodValue&gt;shelly.burton@mtsi-va.com&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Contact&gt;&#13;
                &lt;BusinessClassification&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationType&gt;Small&lt;/OrganizationType&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;BusinessType&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationCategory&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;BusinessOrOrganization&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;IRSDesignation&gt;Corporate Entity, Not Tax Exempt (Pays Federal Income Taxes)&lt;/IRSDesignation&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;ProfitStructure&gt;For-Profit Organization&lt;/ProfitStructure&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/BusinessOrOrganization&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationCategory&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/BusinessType&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/BusinessClassification&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Party to receive Invoice&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0768&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine1&gt;1155 DEFENSE PENTAGON&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine2&gt;WASHINGTON, DC 20301-1155&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAddresses&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ProcurementInstrumentAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ObligatedAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ObligatedAmount&gt;4700000.00&lt;/ObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;FinancialReference&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FinancialCodeDescription&gt;Accounting Classification Reference Number (ACRN)&lt;/FinancialCodeDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FinancialCodeValue&gt;AA&lt;/FinancialCodeValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/FinancialReference&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;LoaDetails&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Blob&gt;^^^097^2020^2021^^0400^000^^255^D^0603699D8Z^^^^^1100^00008522^012215^USRE^OSD - ASD (RESEA^USRE_030603699D8Z795^20_0400D_0603699^255.00 R&amp;amp;D Cont^^^&lt;/Blob&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/LoaDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ObligatedAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Firm Price&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Amount&gt;6853236.60&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Header Only - Total Contract Value&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Amount&gt;6938986.60&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Funded Amount&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Amount&gt;4700000.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/OtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentAmounts&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;HQ0642045897&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Section&gt;C&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
            &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;North American Industry Classification System (NAICS)&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;541715&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Section&gt;C&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/ProcurementInstrumentHeader&gt;&#13;
        &lt;ContractLineItems&gt;&#13;
            &lt;LineItems&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;DFARS&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;LineItem&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemType&gt;CLIN&lt;/LineItemType&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemBase&gt;0001&lt;/LineItemBase&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/LineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/DFARS&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OptionLineItem&gt;false&lt;/OptionLineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PricingArrangementBase&gt;Firm Fixed Price&lt;/PricingArrangementBase&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductOrService&gt;Services&lt;/ProductOrService&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductServiceDescription&gt;RETS IDIQ &amp;#8211; Labor Task order work as described by the Performance Work Statement (PWS). Period of Performance 12/1/2020 - 11/30/2025.&lt;/ProductServiceDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Quantity&gt;12&lt;/Quantity&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ItemUIDRequired&gt;false&lt;/ItemUIDRequired&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PriceBasis&gt;Not to Exceed&lt;/PriceBasis&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;UnitOfMeasure&gt;Months&lt;/UnitOfMeasure&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;UnitPrice&gt;571103.05&lt;/UnitPrice&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Delivery&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ShipToAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Ship To&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0287&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;AlternateIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;Description&gt;Local Code&lt;/Description&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;Value&gt;HQ0287&lt;/Value&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;/AlternateIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;OrganizationName&gt;OUSD RESEARCH AND ENGINEERING&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                        &lt;AddressLine1&gt;3030 DEFENSE PENTAGON, ROOM 3E-172&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                        &lt;AddressLine2&gt;WASHINGTON, DC 20301-3030&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                        &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Contact&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;TitleOrFunction&gt;CHIEF ENGINEER&lt;/TitleOrFunction&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;Name&gt;MARC GOLDENBERG&lt;/Name&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Telephone&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;MethodValue&gt;571-239-7327&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;MethodDescription&gt;Email&lt;/MethodDescription&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;MethodValue&gt;marc.j.goldenberg.civ@mail.mil&lt;/MethodValue&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/ContactMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/Contact&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ShipToAddress&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Delivery&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Firm Price&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;6853236.60&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemDates&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;LineItemDateDescription&gt;Period of Performance&lt;/LineItemDateDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;LineItemPeriod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PeriodStart&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;DateElement&gt;2020-12-01&lt;/DateElement&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/PeriodStart&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PeriodEnd&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;DateElement&gt;2021-11-30&lt;/DateElement&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/PeriodEnd&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/LineItemPeriod&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemDates&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Product Service Code&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;AJ13&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AlternateDescription&gt;Program&lt;/AlternateDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;S10&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Shipping&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PaymentMethod&gt;Contractor&lt;/PaymentMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FoBPoint&gt;Destination&lt;/FoBPoint&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Shipping&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/LineItems&gt;&#13;
            &lt;LineItems&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;DFARS&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;LineItem&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemType&gt;INFOSLIN&lt;/LineItemType&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemBase&gt;0001&lt;/LineItemBase&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemExtension&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;InfoSlinExtension&gt;01&lt;/InfoSlinExtension&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/LineItemExtension&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/LineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/DFARS&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OptionLineItem&gt;false&lt;/OptionLineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductOrService&gt;Services&lt;/ProductOrService&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductServiceDescription&gt;Funding Only for CLIN 0001&lt;/ProductServiceDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ItemUIDRequired&gt;false&lt;/ItemUIDRequired&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ObligatedAmount&gt;4614250.00&lt;/ObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CIN&gt;HQ06420458970001&lt;/CIN&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeDescription&gt;Accounting Classification Reference Number (ACRN)&lt;/FinancialCodeDescription&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeValue&gt;AA&lt;/FinancialCodeValue&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Funded Amount&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;4614250.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;HQ0642045897&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Line Item Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;0001&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/LineItems&gt;&#13;
            &lt;LineItems&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;DFARS&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;LineItem&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemType&gt;CLIN&lt;/LineItemType&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemBase&gt;0002&lt;/LineItemBase&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/LineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/DFARS&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OptionLineItem&gt;false&lt;/OptionLineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PricingArrangementBase&gt;Cost No Fee&lt;/PricingArrangementBase&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductOrService&gt;Services&lt;/ProductOrService&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductServiceDescription&gt;RETS IDIQ - Travel Travel CONUS and OCONUS may be required.  The Contractor will be reimbursed for travel to provide support at a Government site or other site as may be specified and approved by the COR.  All travel shall be approved, by the COR prior to commencement of travel.  The Contractor shall be reimbursed for actual allowable, allocable, and reasonable travel costs incurred during performance of this effort in accordance with FAR 31.205-46, Travel costs.  &#13;
&#13;
This CLIN is established on a Cost Reimbursement basis and will be used for work as described by the Performance Work Statement (PWS).  Period of Performance 12/1/2020 - 11/30/2025.&lt;/ProductServiceDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ItemUIDRequired&gt;false&lt;/ItemUIDRequired&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Addresses&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Acceptance Location&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0034&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS - ACQUISITION DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine1&gt;4800 MARK CENTER DRIVE, SUITE 09F09&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine2&gt;ALEXANDRIA, VA 22350&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AcceptanceInspection&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Action&gt;Acceptance&lt;/Action&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Location&gt;Destination&lt;/Location&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Instructions&gt;None&lt;/Instructions&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/AcceptanceInspection&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Addresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ObligatedAmount&gt;20000.00&lt;/ObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CIN&gt;HQ06420458970002&lt;/CIN&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeDescription&gt;Accounting Classification Reference Number (ACRN)&lt;/FinancialCodeDescription&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeValue&gt;AA&lt;/FinancialCodeValue&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Estimated Cost&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;20000.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Not to Exceed Amount (Funding)&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;20000.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Product Service Code&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;AJ13&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;HQ0642045897&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AlternateDescription&gt;Program&lt;/AlternateDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;S10&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Line Item Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;0002&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Shipping&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PaymentMethod&gt;Contractor&lt;/PaymentMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FoBPoint&gt;Destination&lt;/FoBPoint&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Shipping&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/LineItems&gt;&#13;
            &lt;LineItems&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;DFARS&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;LineItem&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemType&gt;CLIN&lt;/LineItemType&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;LineItemBase&gt;0003&lt;/LineItemBase&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/LineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/DFARS&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemIdentifier&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;OptionLineItem&gt;false&lt;/OptionLineItem&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PricingArrangementBase&gt;Cost No Fee&lt;/PricingArrangementBase&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/PricingArrangement&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductOrService&gt;Services&lt;/ProductOrService&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ProductServiceDescription&gt;RETS IDIQ - Other Direct Costs (ODCs) ODCs as approved by the COR and CO.  Period of Performance 12/1/2020 - 11/30/2025.&lt;/ProductServiceDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ItemUIDRequired&gt;false&lt;/ItemUIDRequired&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ProductServicesOrdered&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemBasicInformation&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Addresses&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AddressDescription&gt;Acceptance Location&lt;/AddressDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Address&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;CountryCode&gt;USA&lt;/CountryCode&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;DoDAAC&gt;HQ0034&lt;/DoDAAC&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;Zone&gt;CONUS&lt;/Zone&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationID&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationName&gt;WHS - ACQUISITION DIRECTORATE&lt;/OrganizationName&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine1&gt;4800 MARK CENTER DRIVE, SUITE 09F09&lt;/AddressLine1&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine2&gt;ALEXANDRIA, VA 22350&lt;/AddressLine2&gt;&#13;
                                    &lt;AddressLine3&gt;US&lt;/AddressLine3&gt;&#13;
                                &lt;/FreeFormAddress&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;/OrganizationAddress&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/OrganizationNameAddress&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/Address&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AcceptanceInspection&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Action&gt;Acceptance&lt;/Action&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Location&gt;Destination&lt;/Location&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Instructions&gt;None&lt;/Instructions&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/AcceptanceInspection&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Addresses&gt;&#13;
                &lt;LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;ObligatedAmount&gt;65750.00&lt;/ObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;CIN&gt;HQ06420458970003&lt;/CIN&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeDescription&gt;Accounting Classification Reference Number (ACRN)&lt;/FinancialCodeDescription&gt;&#13;
                            &lt;FinancialCodeValue&gt;AA&lt;/FinancialCodeValue&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;/FinancialReferenceCode&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemObligatedAmount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Estimated Cost&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;65750.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;AmountDescription&gt;Not to Exceed Amount (Funding)&lt;/AmountDescription&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;Amount&gt;65750.00&lt;/Amount&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/ItemOtherAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/LineItemAmounts&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Product Service Code&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;AJ13&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;HQ0642045897&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;AlternateDescription&gt;Program&lt;/AlternateDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;S10&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceDescription&gt;Purchase Requisition Line Item Number&lt;/ReferenceDescription&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;ReferenceValue&gt;0003&lt;/ReferenceValue&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;Section&gt;B&lt;/Section&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/ReferenceNumber&gt;&#13;
                &lt;Shipping&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;PaymentMethod&gt;Contractor&lt;/PaymentMethod&gt;&#13;
                        &lt;FoBPoint&gt;Destination&lt;/FoBPoint&gt;&#13;
                    &lt;/FoBDetails&gt;&#13;
                &lt;/Shipping&gt;&#13;
            &lt;/LineItems&gt;&#13;
        &lt;/ContractLineItems&gt;&#13;
    &lt;/AwardInstrument&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ProcurementDocument&gt;</content>
        <name>Azure</name>
        <sys_created_by>1370228783.CTR</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2023-01-25 19:10:30</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>18bddf2edb6ca158b1227ea5f396196d</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_updated_by>1370228783.CTR</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2023-01-25 19:10:30</sys_updated_on>
    </x_g_dis_atat_dapps_dummy_data>
</record_update>
]]></payload>
        <sys_class_name>sys_metadata_link</sys_class_name>
        <sys_created_by>1370228783.CTR</sys_created_by>
        <sys_created_on>2023-01-25 20:10:09</sys_created_on>
        <sys_id>7e6ba3aadbeca158b1227ea5f3961971</sys_id>
        <sys_mod_count>0</sys_mod_count>
        <sys_name>Azure</sys_name>
        <sys_package display_value="ATAT" source="x_g_dis_atat">f600233d1b154d507b782f84604bcb12</sys_package>
        <sys_policy/>
        <sys_scope display_value="ATAT">f600233d1b154d507b782f84604bcb12</sys_scope>
        <sys_update_name>sys_metadata_link_7e6ba3aadbeca158b1227ea5f3961971</sys_update_name>
        <sys_updated_by>1370228783.CTR</sys_updated_by>
        <sys_updated_on>2023-01-25 20:10:09</sys_updated_on>
        <tablename>x_g_dis_atat_dapps_dummy_data</tablename>
    </sys_metadata_link>
</record_update>
